https://latinobaseball.com/privacy-of-use/

Privacy Policy for Latino Baseball
At Latino Baseball, accessible from https://latinobaseball.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that are collected and recorded by Latino Baseball and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
Log Files
Latino Baseball follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Like any other website, Latino Baseball uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
For more general information on cookies, please read the “What Are Cookies” article on Cookie Consent website.
Google DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Our Advertising Partners
Some of the advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.
Google
https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Latino Baseball. Our Privacy Policy was created with the help of the Free Privacy Policy Generator and the Privacy Policy Generator Online.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Latino Baseball, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that Latino Baseball has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third-Party Privacy Policies
Latino Baseball’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
Latino Baseball does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Latino Baseball. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYou must be logged in to post a comment.
MOST WATCHED
‘Calle Ocho Live’ event is streaming now!
4 days ago
THIS DAY IN BÉISBOL September 16: Rockies’ Jorge de la Rosa posts 15th win of season
3 weeks ago
THIS DAY IN BÉISBOL September 15: Yasiel Puig’s 3-HR, 7-RBI game
3 weeks ago
News WireLatinx NewswireUnforgettable: From Ivy Queen’s Virtual Duet with Celia Cruz to Hollywood Stars and a Salsa Dance Competition, Calle Ocho Live Hit High Notes and Millions of ViewsPRESS RELEASE - Thu, 08 Oct 2020 21:07:36MIAMI, FL – October 8, 2020 – (LATINX NEWSWIRE) – The Calle Ocho Music Festival may not have been on the streets of Miami this year but for one special afternoon the show’s spirit overcame the pandemic with a Calle Ocho Live virtual event that lived up to its billing. Distributed across more than 40 …Spark Gives Women Cause to Celebrate In 2020PRESS RELEASE - Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:49:56— The First Drive-In Empowerment Event Is A Welcomed Respite from the ‘Pandemic Funk’ —
Focusing on Financial Education for Hispanic Heritage MonthPRESS RELEASE - Thu, 08 Oct 2020 16:53:34Financial literacy helps consumers plan effectively for the future.View More
TRENDING TOPICS News 140
Story 14
History 96
Dominican Day 11
Videos 7
Events 7
Caribbean Series 5
Hall of Fame 5
‘Calle Ocho Live’ event is streaming now!
4 days ago
THIS DAY IN BÉISBOL September 16: Rockies’ Jorge de la Rosa posts 15th win of season
3 weeks ago
THIS DAY IN BÉISBOL September 15: Yasiel Puig’s 3-HR, 7-RBI game
3 weeks ago
Categories
Caribbean Series (5)
Dominican Day (11)
Events (7)
Hall of Fame (5)
History (96)
News (140)
Story (14)
Photos (3)
Stats (4)
Videos (7)
Search for:
